<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Setting Guide</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>

    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>

    <string name="setting_finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="start_using">Start</string>

    <array name="array_finish_item">
        <item>Daling User Agreement</item>
        <item>System update service</item>
    </array>

    <string name="user_agreement_title">
        Terms and Statements
    </string>
    <string name="user_agreement_content">
        Agreement of Usage\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Thank you for using Darling smartphone, in order to provide you with better Internet services, Darling will connects to the network, conduct positioning, or read personal information when necessary, including:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00091. The User Center Service completes your registration more quickly by reading the SMS verification code.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00092. Cloud Sync guarantees data security by synchronizing contacts, short messages and call logs to the Cloud.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00093. Online YPS completes number identification by reading the call logs and short messages, and Mobile Manager intercepts phones and short messages by reading contacts, call logs and short messages.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00094. Push Service, Protruly appstore, Cloud Account, Account Center, Yellow Pages, Network Location, System Interface Tools, Mobile Manager, Weather, Information, Power Management, Network Management, Number Cloud Service will open positioning when connecting to the network to provide more accurate services.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00095. Push Service, Cloud Account, Cloud Sync, Cloud Album, User Center, Account Center, Weather, Mobile Manager, External Application Installation, Video, Information, Media Service, System Framework Service, Search, System Interface Tools, System Desktop, Network Location, Yellow Pages and Power Management need connecting to the network to realize their normal functions.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009For this purpose, you have to pay for data fees, communication fees, information fees and other fees charged by the telecom operators when your Darling smartphone connects to the network. The value-added services you purchase will be charged by the value-added services provider. Please confirm the relevant fees with the value-added service provider.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Your position information may be recorded by our Positioning Service and provided to other services of Darling or the software applications of the third party, and thus we specially warn you to pay careful attention to the position Permission when using the third-party applications, to protect your personal privacy.\n\n\nPrivacy Policy Statement\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Protruly and its partners (referred to as “Protruly”, “our Company”, “we”, or “us”) understand the importance of privacy to the customers, so hereby we strive to explain how we collect, use, disclose, transmit and store your information. This Privacy Policy outlines our approach to information processing.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Protruly has always attached importance to the protection of the privacy of users (including natural persons, legal persons and other organizations obtaining or using this product by whatever legal means, hereinafter referred to as “users” or “you”), and hereby explains to the public the operation method of our products or services, users’ rights and obligations, as well as the collection, usage, storage, safety protection, disclosure of users’ personal information and data, so as to better protect your rights to use this product and your personal information. Before using the product or service, you must carefully read and fully understand the provisions and limitations set out in this Privacy Policy Statement (the “Statement”). This Statement is of independence and integrity. When you choose to use this product, you’ll be deemed as having understood and fully agreed with all the terms specified in this Statement, and voluntarily assuming all responsibilities and risks arising therefrom. If you do not agree with this Statement, please terminate the use of our products or services.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009What personal information we will collect\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009We have two ways to collect information:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00091. The information you provide to us: You may need to provide us with your personal information, such as name, e-mail address, phone number, ID number, and so on when you register an account at Protruly.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00092. The information we collect in the course of your using our products and services: you may need to provide your mailing address, bank account and so on. If necessary, we will also collect information about the use of the products, such as IP address, Cookie, position information, product manufacturer, product model, product unique identifier, device data, etc.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Why we need to collect personal information, mainly for the following two reasons:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00091. Some services cannot be used unless you provide your personal information.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00092. Your personal information may help us to better optimize our products and services, better meet your needs, and provide you with more convenient customized services.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009How we collect personal information:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00091. The information you provide directly\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Some services may require you to provide information directly to us. For example, many of our services allow users to create accounts or personal data. In these services, you may be required to provide certain personal information to set up your account or personal data. For example, when you create an account at Protruly, you may need to submit certain personal information, such as name, phone number, email address, and ID number.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00092. Information about service usage\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009In addition to the information you provide, we may also collect information about your use of our services through the software in your device and otherwise. For example, we may collect:\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Device information - such as hardware model, phone number, IMEI No. and other UDID, MAC add., IP add., operating system version, as well as settings of device for access services.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Log information - such as service usage time and duration, the search queries input through the service, as well as the information stored in the Cookie set on the device.\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Position information - such as information about the device’s IP address, which may be sent to us when you use certain services. (Please note that we are working with the third-party service provider who provides voice-to-text conversion services on behalf of us. The provider may receive and store certain voice commands.) Other information about your use of the services, such as the applications used, the sites visited, and how to interact with the contents provided through the service.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00093. Information from the third party\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009We may obtain your information from publicly available sources (as permitted by law) and may combine them with other information received or related to you. If you choose to connect to a third-party web service, we may also obtain your information from these services.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00094. Other information we collect\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009We may also collect other information about you, your device, or the use of services in other ways, which will be indicated to you upon collection or with your consent.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009You may choose not to provide certain types of information (for example, the information we requested to complete your personal data for a Protruly account), but this may affect your capability to use certain services.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009How we use the personal information collected:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00091. Make service registration for your device;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00092. Provide the services or functions you request;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00093. Provide customized content and make recommendation based on your past use of our services;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00094. Advertising, such as providing customized ads and sponsored content (you may learn more about it through our advertising services) and sending you promotional information;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00095. Evaluate and analyze the market, customers, products and services (including asking for your suggestions on our products and services, and conducting customer surveys);\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00096. Know how you use our services so that we can improve our services and develop new products and services;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00097. Provide maintenance services for your device;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00098. Carry out free prize draw, prize contest or promotions as permitted by law;\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u00099. Other purposes with your consent.\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009How we store and protect personal information:\n\n\u0009\u0009\u0009\u0009Protruly adopts the generally accepted industry safety standards, and takes encryption measures to protect users’ personal identity information and data, so as to ensure that your information will not be accessed, used or disclosed in an unauthorized manner. In terms of technology, Protruly applies anti-virus software, encryption-based protection and monitoring system to enhance its data center’s protection capability against attacks. In regard to the system, Protruly provides safety and privacy protection knowledge training for its employees, to ensure that they all understand the importance of data protection. But based on the inherent defects and operational risks of the network, Protruly cannot guarantee absolute safety of your information.\n
    </string>
</resources>
